spottedfashion.com 2017-07-27

# Privacy Policy – Spotted Fashion

**Privacy Policy**  
Spotted Fashion  
Effective and Last Updated: April 21, 2014

This website is owned and operated by Spotted Fashion. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors while they interact with the content, products and services on this site (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site only. It does not apply to other websites to which we link. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want you to understand what information we collect about you, how we collect it, how that information is used, and how you can control our disclosure of it. You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

**1) Information Collected**

We collect two types of information from you: i) information that you voluntarily provide to us (e.g. through a voluntary registration process, sign-ups or emails); and ii) information that is derived through automated tracking mechanisms.

**Cookies**

Our site uses “cookies” and other tracking technologies. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. If a user’s system is idle for a defined time, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorised access to the user’s information while they are away from their computer.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Site.

Third-Party Cookies: In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognise a unique “cookie” on your browser. Third party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. For more information on Google and cookies, [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

**2) How We Use Your Information**

Spotted Fashion only uses your personal information for the original purposes it was given. Your personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection.

Spotted Fashion will not disclose, use, give or sell any personal information to third parties for any purposes other than to our suppliers and other third parties who need to know in order to deliver services on behalf of Spotted Fashion unless required to do so by law. Further, Spotted Fashion reserves the right to contact you regarding matters relevant to the underlying service provided and/or the information collected.  
Please note that personally identifiable information is used only to provide you with a more enjoyable, convenient online experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation supporting your use of the Site.  
Spotted Fashion may use your personal information for target advertising toward you based on things such as region, gender, interests, goals, habits, etc.

We may permit certain trusted third parties to track usage, analyse data such as the source address that a page request is coming from, your IP address or domain name, the date and time of the page request, the referring Web site (if any) and other parameters in the URL. This is collected in order to better understand our Web site usage, and enhance the performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. We may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the Site; analyse data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your queries.

**4) How We Protect Your Information**

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We take appropriate security measures to protect your information against unauthorised access to or unauthorised alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information and data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

**5) Third Party Advertising**

Advertisements appearing on this Site may be delivered to you by Spotted Fashion or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. Doing this allows the advertising partners to recognise your computer each time they send you an advertisement. In this way, they may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. This information allows an advertising partner to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Spotted Fashion does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertising servers of ad partners.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Spotted Fashion and does not cover the use of cookies by any of its advertisers.

**6) Children’s Privacy and Parental Controls**

We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorised to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that can be used to prevent children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.

**7) Disclaimer to Security**

By consenting to the Terms and Conditions of the Site and hence the Privacy Policy, you consent that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk.

**8) Notification of Changes**

Spotted Fashion reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. If at some point in the future, there is a change to our Privacy Policy, unless we obtain your express consent, such change will only apply to information collected after the revised Privacy Policy took effect. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

**9) CONTACT INFORMATION:**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please contact:  
Spotted Fashion
